The Demon Realm approaches?
You've estimated the potential damage
and planned how we should distribute troops?
Honestly...
Just who do you think you are, Mia?
Miss Mia.
Would you like to escape?
Escape? From this kingdom?
I made time to see you because you
said you had something to tell me.
From this man who sold my sister?
Never...
I'd never do that!
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 6
"Reason and Emotion"
You're starting to take on
your sister's bad habits.
Listen here. Politics is a man's domain.
Furnish funds and forces for something
that might happen every few centuries?
What an outrageous suggestion!
These things cost money, you see?
If I may be so bold, Your Highness...
Were you not generously compensated
when my sister was sent to Parnacorta?
Oh, that...
*Concept
I've already spent most of it on a giant
gold statue of the Girtonian royal family
to be unveiled on the anniversary
of our nation's founding!
This kingdom might really be doomed.
I'll make a gold statue of you too soon!
You spent the money you got for my sister on WHAT?
P-Please, wait!
Out of the way!
The king!
After taking ill, he spends all his time
in his room and rarely sees anyone...
Mia, is the news of the
Demon Realm's approach true?
It is.
Soon, ours will be a land of demons,
unfit for human habitation.
Father, she's just a woman!
There's no need to listen to—
Be quiet!
Nobody knows more
about monsters than a saint.
Not satisfied to send Philia
to another kingdom without my say-so,
you intend to ignore Mia's advice as well?
You absolute fool!
I knew it! Selling Philia
was entirely the prince's idea.
Father, that certainly wasn't my doing!
She insisted on going to help
our poor neighbors—
Even so, it was your duty—as both her
fiancé and prince of this realm—to stop her!
Am I wrong?
Nah.
Please continue, Mia—
Majesty!
Bring Saint Philia's medicine!
Isn't there any left?
No, we're all out.
We have what the castle herbalist made...
What? Don't we have the
recipe my sister left with you?
I'm afraid...
it was lost in error.
What in the world?
Fetch the best we have.
Then the real reason
he sent my sister away...
He wants his father gone
so that he has free rein?
Now, Mia...
Have a little faith in Girtonia's forces.
I firmly believe that any place they
guard is the safest in the world!
It's like he really thinks that's true.
He's even going to ignore
His Majesty's warning.
You needn't worry about a thing.
In that case...
Your Highness?
Despite your heartening reassurances,
I simply find myself so frightened!
Squee!
Squee
Might I ask a favor?
For my duties tomorrow...
Won't you kindly come along?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Kill that thing already!
Hurry! Hurry! Get this one now! This one!
My plan was to bring him to the front line.
The effects of the Demon Realm's
approach have grown stronger,
and it's common to see large
groups of monsters spawn at once.
Now that he's seen it for himself,
he'll have to come to his senses.
Silver Judgment!
M-Mia?
I-I-I'm having a bit of stomach trouble.
I think I might return to the castle.
Mia?
Oh, Your Highness! You're leaving already?
Have you perhaps seen how very dangerous
things have become due to my grave inadequacy?
D-Dangerous? It's not dangerous at all!
You and Girtonia's top troops
are doing a bang-up job!
Is this guy blind or something?
It's not that I'm shaken or anything.
My stomach's genuinely upset,
so I want to go home.
Your Highness, however do you expect
to leave under these conditions?
Wh-Where did they come from?!
If nothing is done, soon the entire
kingdom will be overrun in this fashion.
Try to imagine it. A world where
not even the capital is safe.
I don't take orders from women!
You're trying to imitate Philia, aren't you?
You're not supposed to be like this!
You're just supposed to stand back and smile!
Or are you trying to humiliate
me the way Philia did?
I've been thinking for a while...
he's got some kind of inferiority
complex about my sister, doesn't he?
They're gonna kill me!
Hiding behind his own fiancée? Unbelievable!
What right does he have
to tell a woman her place?
Someone do something! I don't wanna die!
Silver Judgment!
...fault. It's not my fault.
Yes, I see now!
This is all Philia's fault for abandoning us!
I'll recall her and make her slay
all these monsters!
What is wrong with this man?
Parnacorta isn't going
to give my sister back.
Not even if we pay double what they did.
Not even if we pay double?
Philia's hardly worth that much!
All she's good for is putting up
a few halfway-decent barriers!
Mia, what's gotten into you lately?
You're so charming.
You don't need to try to be like her.
You're going to be my wife someday!
Just do your job as unobtrusively as you can.
No matter what I say, he won't learn.
Now, Mia, let's go home!
With the Demon Realm approaching,
what should I do?
Hey there, babe! Wanna take
a little walk with me?
Er...
Need a hand with your things? You're
gorgeous! What's your name, honey?
You'd better...
knock it off!
Sheesh.
That was mean, Big Sis.
Next time you do that, it won't just
be your head. I'll slice you to bits.
I'd prefer to avoid that.
I'll die if you slice up my you-know-what.
Honestly...
I'm here worried about the revival
of the archdemon Asmodeus,
and you're as calm as can be.
I mean, he and I are kind of family and all.
Doesn't he rank way higher than you?
Not that much higher.
His soul was sealed away
by Saint Fianna four hundred years ago,
but the approach of the Demon Realm
has weakened the seal.
If something were to happen...
He'd be back in a snap, right?
Erza's Familiar
Mammon the Demon
That's why the church sent us, remember?
Archbishop's Personal Exorcist,
Church of Cremoux Main Branch
Erza Notice
See?
That hurts!
So let's get going.
Yeah, yeah.
Damn it!
Ever since I sold Philia off,
my life's been unending misery.
How badly must she humiliate
me before she's through?
Since I was a child, I've done my best to live
up to the expectations of those around me.
The crown prince is a useless shut-in.
Everyone said it was the kingdom's
wunderkind, the second prince,
who deserved to take the throne.
It was a perfect life.
Yes... until that day.
Perfect saint, my eye!
Physical beauty is all a woman needs.
Just smile and be charming already!
She tells men what to do,
and even ignores my opinions!
You're absolutely right about that.
Marquis Pyrz!
When did you get here?
I've been here for a while, Your Highness.
I have some information for you.
What is it?
I believe it's time to show the saint...
rather, the brat you sold to our neighbor,
the true power of the kingdom's wunderkind.
My true power?
That's right.
Did you know that we still have a treasure
left by Saint Fianna stored away?
A treasure of Fianna's?
First I've heard of it.
They say it lies beneath
the church in the capital.
It is a ring containing all the magic power
of the legendary Saint Fianna.
Whoever breaks the seal
will gain tremendous power!
If you were the one to do it
and wield such power...
No one could tell me what to do ever again!
Yes.
You could even show up that obnoxious
saint in the next kingdom over!
I love it!
I'll show her my superiority!
Even Mia couldn't deny it...
And neither could my father!
I wish that old geezer
would just die already!
What's this?
When did I get here?
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
R-Return her?!
We're supposed to send Saint Philia back now?
It seems things in Girtonia
are worse than anticipated.
Obviously, we're well within
our rights to deny them,
but I wanted to inform you.
I have to stay here in the capital to
maintain the Great Purification Circle.
That's why I sent Himari
to help Mia work out a plan, but...
I suspect Prince Julius has overruled her.
What should I do?
Miss Philia.
Don't shoulder this burden alone.
Take a look around you.
We just need to improve
conditions in Girtonia, right?
As a potential compromise,
I've proposed sending Parnacorta's
knights to aid them.
The knights?
Yes.
Not to boast, but they're quite competent.
Leonardo is a former knight
I'm sure they could be of service
to Miss Mia in Girtonia as well.
I feel some responsibility
for the situation, myself.
I'd like to help her as much as I can.
So you don't have to worry.
Thank you, Prince Osvalt.
I-I'm sorry. I should have offered you tea.
Lena, please help me!
Coming!
At least she's learning to ask
for help in her daily life.
Yes, though I wish she'd ask
for something just for herself.
Agreed.
Open your eyes, Grace.
It worked. You've done very well.
Remember that feeling just now.
I will!
Pardon me.
Saint Philia, I've received word from Himari.
Let's take a break.
I'd heard Girtonia's king was in poor health,
but I never imagined...
They destroyed the recipe
for making his medicine?
That's awful!
There's more in Mia's letter
that I haven't told them.
She's certain that Prince Julius is
behind the machinations in Girtonia.
She's trying to take him down politically.
My warm and kind sister who
never wanted to hurt anyone...
She's prepared to go to such lengths?
What's happening over there?
Let us send the recipe via Himari.
I've made improvements to it,
so it may even cure the king altogether.
Also, tell Mia not to do anything reckless.
I shall.
If the king recovers,
the nations politics may stabilize.
Working with Parnacorta's knights
to defend the kingdom
should take some burden off of Mia.
She won't have to push herself.
This will be enough.
At least, it should be...
But for some reason,
I feel like I can't breathe.
Mia, please be safe.
So it turns out Prince Julius really is
the one messing everything up.
I see. Shall I eliminate Prince Julius, then?
Kill him? That's quite a leap!
I think poison may be the most effective way.
For instance, a dart to the bloodstream
from a blowpipe
could spell an immediate demise.
Wait just a minute!
All we need to do is strip him of his power.
If someone were to blame Parnacorta for the
assassination, it could lead to all-out war.
If you insist, I'll call off the murder.
Regarding the king's medicine,
I'll ask Philia about it in my next missive.
Yes, please do.
Now, as for Prince Julius...
How do you wish to handle him?
How do I...?
I want him to pay in full
for how he treated my sister,
apologize sincerely,
repent his foolishness, and,
after he's stripped of status and fortune,
I want him thrown out of the kingdom!
Through your position as saint,
that might well be possible.
That's right. I'm the saint.
The protector of this kingdom
and the savior of its people.
Can I really act on such a personal grudge?
When this is all over, will I
still be able to remain saint?
I don't even remember the kind
of saint I wanted to be...
That's all for lessons today.
Adenauer Household  3 Years Prior
You did very well, Mia.
Ma'am!
Mia Adenauer, Age 15
That's right. I heard the news!
Your older sister, Philia,
got her certification,
and tomorrow she'll make
her debut as a saint!
Congratulations!
Y-Yes... Thank you!
N-No one said anything to me!
The Next Day
Why didn't Mother and
Father tell me about it?
Listen, Mia.
It was Philia's idea to leave home and train
at the church to become a proper saint.
To respect her wishes, we should
limit contact with her in the future.
My sister, Philia, is one year older than me.
For as long as I can remember,
we haven't lived together.
I've barely ever gotten to talk to her!
Even though we're sisters?
But that's all the more reason...
I've just gotta find out more!
As part of my sister's saintly debut,
she's going to create Pillars
of Light near the capital.
That might be a shortcut!
I even put on a disguise so that my mother
won't recognize me if she spots me!
A monster?!
How?! There's a barrier around the capital!
It's supposed to be safe here!
Am I going to die?
I know it's my own fault...
Because I come from a saintly bloodline,
yet I never trained.
Because I thought I could
leave it all to my sister,
and I never bothered to learn anything...
Not even how dangerous it
is outside the city!
Help me, God!
Silver Judgment!
Are you all right?
I hope I made it in time.
Philia, where have you gone?
GASP
I'll call the guard. I must return
to the ceremony. Farewell.
She's like a hero!
That was my reintroduction to her.
Wow, two pillars already!
So fast!
Our new saint is the most
powerful in history by far!
She's incredible...
Amazing!
I wanted to become a saint like Philia.
That's right... That's
what I wished for that day.
To help people regardless of standing.
To become a shield protecting my kingdom.
The greatest saint of all time,
my role model, my north star...
my sister always took to the front
line with all her might.
Even when she was outcast, even
when she left, she didn't complain.
She didn't blame anyone, spite
anyone, or consider revenge.
She just silently prayed
for the safety of others.
I know that...
I can't sacrifice that
for the sake of my revenge.
But... I can't stand it!
The people who were so cruel
to the person I admire, I just...
I hate them! I hate them all!
I understand things rationally,
but my emotions won't listen.
I'm all jumbled up.
I don't know what to do.
Miss Mia.
That's just fine.
Remain true to yourself and be honest.
Don't push yourself to become Saint Philia.
It's not always good for there to be
an obvious right and wrong.
Moreover, a person's true heart
is not always clear to themselves.
There are a million ways for it to be.
As long as you press forward, I believe you'll
work through your feelings someday.
You should be who you are,
working to save the kingdom in your own way.
In my own way?
That's going to be even harder
than choking back my anger.
Nevertheless, this fury... let it be the
kindling that sets my heart ablaze.
Even if it's hard, even if it hurts,
I'll do whatever it takes.
Fine. Then let's do this.
I'm going to keep hating that awful man
and, as part of my saintly obligations,
I shall expose his rotten schemes
and completely break him!
Selfish as I am, I demand both the
salvation of my kingdom and revenge!
That's the way the 29th saint,
Mia Adenauer, does things!
What shall we do first, then?
First, I need someone else to entrust
political matters to until the king recovers.
Someone else?
You mean...
Indeed, there is someone else
in the kingdom suited to the task.
We'll call upon the crown prince confined
to his room by Prince Julius's supporters...
Prince Fernand!
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside by
My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 7:
Next Time
Episode 7
"The Imprisoned Prince"
"The Imprisoned Prince."